Robert Rauschenberg papers RRFA.01 RRFA.01.TEST
RRF Test Repository
- Printed Materials
  - Rauschenberg, Robert
    - Exhibitions
      - Group
        - "300 Artists to the Support of the NY Studio School", 1976 (Box PM7)
        - Metropolitan Museum of Art: "Contemporary American Prints", 1976 (Box PM7)
        - Fendrick Gallery: "Selections from Untitled Press Inc.", 1976 (Box PM7)
        - Renwick Gallery, National Collection of Fine Arts, Smithsonian Institution: "The Object as Poet", 1976 (Box PM7)
        - Marian Goodman Gallery: "Objects!", 1977 (Box PM7)
        - New Orleans Museum of Art: "Five From Louisiana", 1977 (Box PM7)
        - John Berggruen Gallery: "American Paintings and Drawings", 1977 (Box PM7)
        - Sonnabend Gallery: "Works From the Collection of Change, Inc.", 1977 (Box PM7)
        - Griffiths Arts Center Gallery: "St. Lawrence University Exhibition of Annual Acquisitions", 1977 (Box PM7)
        - New York State Museum: "The State of Art", 1977 (Box PM14)
        - Centre Georges Pompidou, Musée National d'Art Moderne: "Paris—New York", 1977 (Box PM7)
        - Hayden Gallery, Massachusetts Institute of Technology: "Paper Forms", 1977 (Box PM7)
        - Syracuse University: "Critics' Choice", 1977 (Box PM7)
        - Renwick Gallery, National Collection of Fine Arts (NCFA): "New Ways With Paper", 1978 (Box PM7)
        - University Gallery, University of Massachusetts/Amherst: "Sets for Cunningham: Johns, Rauschenberg, Warhol", 1978 (Box PM7)
        - James E. West Alumni Center, UCLA: "Words and Images", 1978 (Box PM7)
        - Leo Castelli, 1978 (Box PM7)
        - Whitney Museum of American Art: "Art About Art", 1978 (Box PM7)
        - Newport Harbor Art Museum: "American Painting of the 1970s", 1979 (Box PM7)
        - Corcoran Gallery of Art: "The 36th Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary American Painting", 1979 (Box PM7)
        - Castelli Uptown: "Drawings by Castelli Artists", 1979 (Box PM7)
        - Whitney Museum of American Art, Downtown Branch: "Auto Icons", 1979 (Box PM7)
        - Rosa Esman Gallery: "Summer Summary", 1979 (Box PM7)
        - Daniel Templon: "Une Peinture Américaine", 1979 (Box PM7)
        - Metropolitan Museum of Art: "Summer Loan Exhibition", 1979 (Box PM7)
        - University Art Museum, University of New Mexico: "A Sense of Scale", 1979 (Box PM7)
        - Richard Hines Gallery: "Fall Exhibition", 1979 (Box PM7)
        - Galerie Denise René Hans Mayer: "Joseph Beuys, Robert Rauschenberg, Andy Warhol", 1979 (Box PM7)
        - Wichita Art Museum: "Wichita Salutes Orleans with Works by 50 Contemporary American Artists", 1979 (Box PM7)
        - Thomas Segal Gallery: "New Handmade Papers, Prints, and Drawings", 1979 (Box PM7)
        - Alex Rosenberg Gallery: "Transworld Art Retrospective", 1980 (Box PM14)
        - University of South Florida: "Five in Florida", 1980 (Box PM7a)
        - Visual Arts Museum, School of Visual Arts: "Contemporary American Drawing", 1980 (Box PM7a)
        - Pace Gallery: "Major Works of the 60s", 1980 (Box PM7a)
        - Aldrich Museum of Contemporary Art: "Changes", 1980 (Box PM7a)
        - Elaine Benson Gallery, Inc.: "The Presidents Show", 1980 (Box PM7a)
        - Fine Arts Gallery, University of South Florida: "Fabrications", 1980 (Box PM7a)
        - Castelli Graphics: "Amalgam", 1980 (Box PM7a)
        - Brooklyn Museum: "American Drawings in Black and White: 1970-1980" (Box PM7a)
        - Walker Art Center: "Artist and Printer: Six American Print Studios", 1980 (Box PM7a)
        - Mary and Leigh Block Gallery, Northwestern University: "Collaborations", 1980 (Box PM7a)
        - John & Marble Ringling Museum of Art: "International Florida Artists Exhibition", 1980 (Box PM7a)
        - National Gallery of Art: "Contemporary American Prints & Drawings 1940-1980", 1981 (Box PM7a)
        - Los Angeles County Museum of Art: "Art and Technology", 1981 (Box PM7a)
        - American Academy of Arts and Sciences: "The Life of the Mind: Unity and Diversity", 1981 (Box PM7a)
        - Margo Leavin Gallery: "Cast, Carved & Constructed: An Exhibition of Contemporary American Sculpture", 1981 (Box PM7a)
        - Middlesbrough Art Gallery: "5th International Drawing Biennale", 1981 (Box PM7a)
        - Pratt Manhattan Center Gallery: "For Love and Money: Dealers Choice", 1981 (Box PM7a)
        - Neuberger Museum, SUNY Purchase: "Soundings", 1981 (Box PM7a)
        - Castelli Graphics: "The New York Collection for Stockholm", 1981 (Box PM7a)
        - Solomon & Co. Fine Art, 1981 (Box PM7a)
        - Edward Thorp Gallery: "Contemporary Drawing", 1981 (Box PM7a)
        - University Gallery, Memphis State University: "Southern Monumental Exhibition", 1981 (Box PM14)
        - General, 1982 (Box PM7a)
        - Sarah Campbell Blaffer Gallery, University of Houston: "New American Paperworks", 1982 (Box PM7a)
        - Galerie Bruno Bischofberger: "Homage to Leo Castelli", 1982 (Box PM7a)
        - Sarah Campbell Blaffer Gallery, University of Houston: "New American Paperworks", 1982 (Box PM14)
        - The New York School: "Four Decades", 1982 (Box PM7a)
        - Edith C. Blum Art Institute, Avery Center for the Arts, Bard College: "The Rebounding Surface: A Study of Reflections in the Work of Nineteen Contemporary Artists", 1982 (Box PM7a)
        - General, 1983 (Box PM14)
        - Palm Press Ltd.: "Prints from the Untitled Press", 1983 (Box PM7a)
        - "Art for a Nuclear Weapons Freeze", 1983 (Box PM7a)
        - General, 1984 (Box PM14)
        - Pratt Manhattan Center Gallery: "From the Beginning", 1984 (Box PM7a)
        - Castelli Graphics: "Fifteenth Anniversary Exhibition", 1984 (Box PM7a)
        - Brooke Alexander, Inc.: "Icons of the Sixties", 1984 (Box PM7a)
        - Los Angeles County Museum of Art: "Olympic Gestures", 1984 (Box PM7a)
        - Visual Arts Museum, School of Visual Arts: "Collage Expanded", 1984 (Box PM7a)
        - National Gallery of Art: "Gemini G.E.L.: Art and Collaboration", 1984 (Box PM7a)
        - General, 1985 (Box PM14)
        - De Cordova and Dana Museum and Park: "Recent Acquisitions: 1980-1984", 1985 (Box PM7a)
        - Museum of Contemporary Art, Los Angeles: "The Panza Collection", 1985 (Box PM7a)
        - Smith College Museum of Art: "Dorothy C. Miller: With an Eye to American Art", 1985 (Box PM7a)
        - Aldrich Museum: "The Classic Tradition", 1985 (Box PM7a)
        - Aldrich Museum of Contemporary Art: "A Second Talent: Painters and Sculptors Who Are also Photographers", 1985 (Box PM14)
        - Edison Community College: "Selections from the Leif Johnson Collection 1965-1985" (Box PM14)
        - General, 1986 (Box PM14)
        - Städtische Galerie im Lenbachhaus: "Beuys zu Ehren", 1986 (Box PM14)
        - Barbara B. Mann Performing Arts Hall: "Examples of Lithographs from ULAE Studios", 1986 (Box PM7a)
        - Museum of Fine Arts, Santa Fe: "Poetics of Space", 1986 (Box PM7a)
        - National Museum of American Art: "Treasures from the National Museum of American Art", 1986 (Box PM7a)
        - Blue Hill Cultural Center: "A Matter of Scale", 1986 (Box PM7a)
        - Sogetsu Art Museum: "Contemporary Art Exhibition to Commemorate Sogetsu 60th Anniversary", 1986 (Box PM14)
        - Museum of Contemporary Art: "Individuals: A Selected History of Contemporary Art, 1945–1986" (Box PM14)
        - The BMW Gallery: "Art Car", 1986 (Box PM14)
        - General, 1987 (Box PM7a)
        - University Art Museum, University of California, Berkeley: "Made in U.S.A.: An Americanization in Modern Art, the 50s and the 60s", 1987 (Box PM14)
        - Edith C. Blum Art Institute, Avery Center for the Arts, Bard College: "The Arts at Black Mountain College, 1933–1957", 1987 (Box PM7a)
        - General, 1988 (Box PM7a)
        - Helander Gallery: "Five Floridians", 1988 (Box PM7a)
        - Museum of Modern Art: "Committed to Print", 1988 (Box PM7a)
        - Galerie Lelong: "Gordon Matta-Clark and Friends", 1988 (Box PM7a)
        - Lucio Amelio: "Oggetto" (2 folders), 1988 (Box PM7a, Box PM15)
        - University Center Gallery, Adelphi University: "The Artist and the Choreographer", 1988 (Box PM7a)
        - Castelli Graphics: "Castelli Graphics 1969-1988" (Box PM7a)
        - Goethe-Institut Osaka: "Art Kites", 1988 (Box PM8)
        - The Penson Gallery: "Altered Images", 1988 (Box PM8)
        - Whitney Museum of American Art, Downtown Branch: "Identity: Representations of the Self", 1988 (Box PM8)
        - General, 1989 (Box PM14)
        - Stux Gallery: "Pre-Pop Post-Appropriation", 1989 (Box PM8)
        - The Harcus Gallery: "Altered States", 1989 (Box PM8)
        - USF Art Museum: "Made in Florida", 1989 (Box PM8)
        - Whitney Museum of American Art, Fairfield County: "The Junk Aesthetic: Assemblage of the 1950s and early 1960s", 1989 (Box PM8)
        - Helsinki Art Hall: "Modern Masters '89", 1989 (Box PM8)
        - Walker Art Center: "First Impressions", 1989 (Box PM8)
        - Basel Art Fair: "America", 1989 (Box PM8)
        - Feigen & Co.: "Filling the Gap", 1989 (Box PM8)
        - Tavelli Gallery: "Medium Cool", 1989 (Box PM8)
        - Whitney Museum of American Art: "20th Century Drawings", 1988-1989 (Box PM8)
        - General, 1990 (Box PM14)
        - Schafler Gallery: "Prints of the Eighties", 1990 (Box PM8)
        - Franklin Furnace Archive: "Contemporary Illustrated Books", 1990 (Box PM8)
        - Wexner Center for the Visual Arts, Ohio State University: "Art in Europe and America: The 1950s and 1960s", 1990 (Box PM8)
        - Scott Hanson Gallery: "Token Gestures: A Painting Show", 1990 (Box PM8)
        - Heland Wetterling Gallery: "Knoedler Gallery Artists", 1990 (Box PM8)
        - Shafrazi Gallery: "American Masters of the 60's", 1990 (Box PM8)
        - James Goodman Gallery: "Pop on Paper", 1990 (Box PM8)
        - Modus Viviendi: "Pools", 1990 (Box PM8)
        - Hofstra University Museum: "The Transparent Thread: Asian Philosophy in Recent American Art", 1990 (Box PM8)
        - Museum of Modern Art: "High & Low Culture: Modern Art and Popular Culture", 1990 (Box PM8)
        - National Gallery of Canada: "Contemporary American Prints from the Carol and Morton Rapp Collection", 1990 (Box PM8)
        - Katonah Museum of Art: "The Technological Muse", 1990 (Box PM8)
        - Galleria il Gabbiano: "Realtá e Visione", 1990 (Box PM8)
        - General, 1991 (Box PM14)
        - El Centro Cultural / Arte Contemporáneo: "El Sueño de Egipto, 1991 (Box PM8)
        - Fay Gold Gallery: "Outside America: Going Into the 90's", 1991 (Box PM8)
        - Guild Hall East Hampton: "Aspects of Collage", 1991 (Box PM8)
        - Institute of Contemporary Art, University of Pennsylvania: "Interactions: Collaborators in the Visual and Performing Arts", 1991 (Box PM8)
        - Whitney Museum of American Art: "Drawing Acquisitions, 1980-1991" (Box PM8)
        - Whitney Museum of American Art, Downtown Branch: "Constructing American Identity", 1991 (Box PM8)
        - Museum of Contemporary Art, Los Angeles: "High & Low: Modern Art and Popular Culture", 1991 (Box PM8)
        - Guild Hall East Hampton: "A View from the Sixties", 1991 (Box PM8)
        - Museum of Modern Art: "Seven Master Printmakers: Innovations in the 1980s", 1991 (Box PM14)
        - Royal Academy of the Arts, London: "Pop Art", 1991 (Box PM8)
        - National Gallery of Art: "Graphicstudio: Contemporary Art from the Collaborative Workshop at the University of South Florida", 1991 (Box PM8)
        - Tampa Museum of Art: "Graphicstudio/U.S.F.: Collaborations in Contemporary Art", 1991 (Box PM8)
        - Fernbank Museum of Natural History: "Picturing Paradise: Art and the Rainforests", 1991 (Box PM8)
        - Galerie Nichido: "Lichtenstein, Rauschenberg, Rosenquist", 1991 (Box PM14)
        - General, 1992 (Box PM14)
        - Stephen Solovy Fine Art: "Drawings for the Stage", 1992 (Box PM8)
        - Museum Ludwig: "Pop Art", 1992 (Box PM8)
        - Museu de Belas Artes Rio de Janeiro—Brasil: "...Reperti...", 1992 (Box PM8)
        - Museum of Contemporary Art, Los Angeles: "Hand-Painted Pop: American Art in Transition, 1955–1962", 1992 (Box PM14a)
        - General, 1993 (Box PM8)
        - Sarah Campbell Blaffer Gallery, University of Houston: "Darkness and Light: Twentieth-Century Works from Texas Collections", 1993 (Box PM14a)
        - San Francisco Museum of Modern Art: "The Anderson Collection Gift of American Pop Art", 1993 (Box PM8)
        - Galerie Hassfurther: "Pop Art", 1993 (Box PM8)
        - Chicago Cultural Center: "The Nature of the Machine, An Exhibition of Kinetic and Biokinetic Art", 1993 (Box PM8)
        - Lucio Amelio S.R.L.: Trismegisto, 1993 (Box PM8)
        - Fogg Art Museum, Harvard University Art Museums: "American Paintings at Mid-Century", 1993 (Box PM8)
        - 20th International Biennial of Graphic Art, International Centre of Graphic Art: "The Exhibition of the Grand Prize Winners from 1955 to 1991", 1993 (Box PM8)
        - Taejon International Expo'93: "Renewing Our Earth", 1993 (Box PM8)
        - Kunsthalle Wien: "Die Sprache der Kunst", 1993 (Box PM8)
        - Museum of Contemporary Art, Los Angeles: "Rolywholyover A Circus", 1993 (Box PM8)
        - Musée d'Art Contemporain: "Peinture: Emblèmes et Références", 1993 (Box PM8)
        - Galerie Beyeler: "New York on Paper", 1993 (Box PM14a)
        - Whitney Museum of American Art at Champion: "Spheres of Influence", 1993 (Box PM14a)
        - General, 1994 (Box PM8)
        - Museum of Art, Fort Lauderdale: "Pop Art: The 1960s and Beyond", 1994 (Box PM8)
        - Cleveland Center for Contemporary Art: "Outside the Frame: Performance and the Object", 1994 (Box PM8)
        - Newton Arts Center: "After the 'Accident': The Unpredictable Print", 1994 (Box PM8)
        - Museum of Contemporary Art, Chicago: "Under Development: Dreaming the MCA's Collection", 1994 (Box PM8)
        - American Academy in Rome: "American Art in Italian Private Collections", 1994 (Box PM8)
        - City Art Centre, Edinburgh: "Worlds in a Box", 1994 (Box PM8)
        - Museum of Modern Art: "A Century of Artists Books", 1994 (Box PM8)
        - Walker Art Center: "Duchamp's Leg", 1994 (Box PM8)
        - Offshore Gallery: "Seasights", 1994 (Box PM8)
        - Susan Sheehan Gallery: "The First Meeting of the Satie Club", 1994 (Box PM14a)
        - General, 1995 (Box PM14a)
        - Cornell Fine Arts Museum, Rollins College: "Reverberations: Diptychs & Triptychs from the Southeast Museum of Photography", 1995 (Box PM8)
        - Ludwig Museum im Deutschherrenhaus, Städtische Museen Koblenz: "Klangskulpturen—Augenmusik", 1995 (Box PM8)
        - Palais des Nations, Geneva: "Dialogues of Peace/Dialogues de paix", 1995 (Box PM8)
        - Center for Curatorial Studies, Bard: "Sniper's Nest: Art That Has Lived with Lucy R. Lippard", 1995 (Box PM8)
        - Susan Sheehan Gallery: "The Big Picture: Large Scale Works on Paper of the 20th Century", 1995 (Box PM14a)
        - Susan Sheehan Gallery: "The Appropriated Image", 1995 (Box PM14a)
        - Contemporary Arts Center, Cincinnati: "It's Only Rock and Roll: Rock and Roll Currents in Contemporary Art", 1995 (Box PM14a)
        - General, 1996 (Box PM14a)
        - Museo Nacional de Bellas Artes: "Arte en el cielo", 1996 (PM8a)
        - Centre Georges Pompidou, Musée National d'Art Moderne: "L'Informe: mode d'emploi", 1996 (PM8a)
        - Museum of Modern Art: "Thinking Print: Books to Billboards, 1980-95", 1996 (PM8a)
        - Padiglione d'Art Contemporanea: "Omaggio a Leo Castelli", 1996 (PM8a)
        - The Art Museum, Florida International University: "Miami Pops!", 1996 (PM8a)
        - Winston Wächter Fine Art: "Pop: Then and Now, A Selection of Work", 1996 (PM8a)
        - Miami Art Museum: "Dream Collection Gifts", 1996 (PM8a)
        - General, 1997 (Box PM14a)
        - Murray Feldman Gallery, Pacific Design Center: "Gemini G.E.L.: Celebrating Thirty Years", 1997 (Box PM14a)
        - Dallas Museum of Art: "Contemporary Art 1950-2000: Movements & Figures", 1997 (PM8a)
        - Sezon Museum of Art: "Proof Positive: Forty Years of Contemporary American Printmaking at ULAE, 1957–1997" (PM8a)
        - Museum of Modern Art: "Objects of Desire: The Modern Still Life", 1997 (PM8a)
        - Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum: "From Dürer to Rauschenberg: A Quintessence of Drawing, Masterworks from the Albertina and the Guggenheim", 1997 (PM8a)
        - Galleria d'Arte Moderna e Contemporanea: "Dadaismo, Dadaismi: Da Duchamp a Warhol", 1997 (PM8a)
        - Haus der Kunst, Munich: "Deep Storage: Arsenale der Erinnerung (Arsenal of Memory)", 1997 (Box PM14a)
        - Andersen Window Gallery, Walker Art Center: "Art of the 1960s: Media is the Message", 1997 (PM8a)
        - Leo Castelli: "The Artists of the Castelli Gallery 1957–1997: Forty Years of Exploration and Innovation, Part One" (PM8a)
        - General, 1998 (Box PM14a)
        - World Health Organization Headquarters, Geneva: "The Edge of Awareness", 1998 (PM8a)
        - Biblioteca Luis Ángel Arango: "Graphicstudio: El Campo Expandido de la Gráfica", 1998 (PM8a)
        - Museum of Contemporary Art, Los Angeles: "Out of Actions: Between Performance and the Object, 1949–1979", 1998 (Box PM14a)
        - General, 1999 (Box PM14a)
        - Winston Wächter Fine Art: "Pop", 1999 (Box PM14a)
        - Paine Webber Art Gallery: "Comfort Zone: Furniture by Artists", 1999 (PM8a)
        - Marcel Sitcoske Gallery: "Re: Rauschenberg", 1999 (PM8a)
        - Friends of Photography, Ansel Adams Center: "Innovation/Imagination: Fifty Years of Polaroid Photography", 1999 (PM8a)
        - Whitney Museum of American Art: "The American Century: Art and Culture 1900–2000, Part II, 1950–2000", 1999 (PM8a)
        - Miami Art Museum: "New Acquisitions: Dream Collection", 1999 (Box PM14a)
        - Museum of Contemporary Art, Los Angeles: "Panza: The Legacy of a Collector", 1999 (Box PM14a)
        - General, 2000 (Box PM14a)
        - Knoedler and Company: "Pasted Pictures: Collage and Abstraction in the Twentieth Century", 2000 (PM8a)
        - Museum of Modern Art: "Making Choices", 2000 (PM8a)
        - Museum of Contemporary Art, Chicago: "Age of Influence: Reflections in the Mirror of American Culture", 2000 (PM8a)
        - John and Mable Ringling Museum of Art: "Sarasota Biennial", 2000 (PM8a)
        - Rooseum Center for Contemporary Art: "Century of Innocence: The History of the White Monochrome", 2000 (PM8a)
        - Tate Modern: "Performing Bodies: Masquerade", 2000 (PM8a)
        - United Nations Visitors' Lobby: "For a Better World: Posters from the United Nations 1945 to Present", 2000 (PM8a)
        - National Gallery of Art: "Twentieth-Century American Art: The Ebsworth Collection", 2000 (Box PM14a)
        - Austin Museum of Art: "The New Frontier: Art and Television, 1960–65", 2000 (Box PM14a)
        - General, 2001 (Box PM14a)
        - Blanton Museum of Art, University of Texas, Austin: "Rembrandt to Rauschenberg: Building the Collection", 2001 (PM8a)
        - Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum: "The Global Guggenheim: Selections from the Extended Collection", 2001 (PM8a)
        - Museum of Contemporary Art, Los Angeles: "A Room of Their Own: From Rothko to Rauschenberg", 2001 (Box PM14a)
        - Centre Georges Pompidou, Musée National d'Art Moderne: "Les Années Pop: 1956–1968 (The Pop years)", 2001 (PM8a)
        - Joslyn Art Museum: "An American Anthem: 300 Years of Painting from the Butler Institute of American Art", 2001 (PM8a)
        - Rose Art Museum, Brandeis University: "A Defining Generation: Then and Now, 1961 and 2001" (PM8a)
        - National Gallery of Art: "Best Impressions: Thirty-five Years of Prints and Sculpture from Gemini G.E.L.", 2001 (PM8a)
        - General, 2002 (Box PM14a)
        - Von Liebig Art Center: "America's Leading Pop Artists, Selections from the University of South Florida Contemporary Art Museum", 2002 (PM8a)
        - Sonnabend Gallery: "The Story of E.A.T.: Experiments in Art and Technology 1960-2002" (PM8a)
        - Meridian International Center: "True Colors: Meditations on the American Spirit", 2002 (PM8a)
        - Tang Teaching Museum and Art Gallery, Skidmore College: "From Pop to Now: Selections from the Sonnabend Collection", 2002 (PM8a)
        - Museum of Modern Art, Queens: "To Be Looked At: Painting and Sculpture from the Collection", 2002 (PM8a)
        - Selby Gallery, Ringling School of Art and Design: "REAL(ist) Men", 2002 (Box PM14a)
        - Charles H. Wright Museum of African American History: "In the Spirit of Martin: The Living Legacy of Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr.", 2002 (Box PM14a)
        - Addison Gallery of American Art, Phillips Academy: "Trisha Brown: Dance and Art in Dialogue, 1961–2001", 2002 (Box PM14a)
        - Whitney Museum of American Art: "An American Legacy, a Gift to New York", 2002 (Box PM14a)
        - Miami Art Museum: "Miami Currents: Linking Collection and Community", 2002 (Box PM14a)
        - General, 2003 (Box PM14a)
        - NTT InterCommunication Center, Tokyo: "E.A.T.—The Story of Experiments in Art and Technology", 2003 (Box PM14a)
        - Frederick R. Weisman Art Museum, University of Minnesota: "Trace Evidence", 2003 (Box PM14a)
        - Guggenheim Hermitage Museum: "American Pop Icons", 2003 (Box PM14a)
        - Janice Mason Art Museum: "The Wier Show: Contemporary Art from the Private Collection of Pat and Dick Wier", 2003 (Box PM14a)
        - Baltimore Museum of Art: "Work Ethic", 2003 (Box PM14a)
        - Tate Liverpool: "Art, Lies and Videotape: Exposing Performance", 2003 (PM8a)
        - Miami Art Museum, Between Art and Life: "From Joseph Cornell to Gabriel Orozco", 2003 (PM8a)
        - Dumbo Arts Center: "Sixth Annual Winter Auction", 2005 (PM8a)
        - General, 2006 (PM8a)
        - Haus der Kunst: "Black Paintings", 2006 (PM8a)
        - Gagosian Gallery: "Pop Art Is.. .", 2007 (Box PM15)
        - Istituto Veneto di Scienze Lettere ed Arti: "Glasstress", 2009 (PM8a)
        - Gemini G.E.L. at Joni Moisant Weyl: "Pacific Standard Editions", 2011 (PM8a)
      - Solo and Two-Person
        - Galleria dell'Obelisco: "Bob Rauschenberg: Scatole e Feticci Personali", 1953 (Box PM9)
        - Stable Gallery: "Rauschenberg: Paintings and Sculpture; Cy Twombly: Paintings and Drawings", 1953 (Box PM9)
        - Galleria la Tartaruga: "Rauschenberg", 1959 (Box PM14b)
        - Leo Castelli: "Robert Rauschenberg", 1960 (Box PM9)
        - Galerie 22: "Rauschenberg, Twombly: zwei amerikanische Maler", 1960 (Box PM14b)
        - Galerie Daniel Cordier: "Robert Rauschenberg", 1961 (Box PM14b)
        - Galleria dell'Ariete, Milan: "Rauschenberg", 1961 (Box PM9)
        - Leo Castelli: "Rauschenberg", 1961 (Box PM9)
        - Leo Castelli: "Rauschenberg", 1963 (Box PM9)
        - Galerie Ileana Sonnabend: "Rauschenberg", 1964 (Box PM9)
        - Gian Enzo Sperone Arte Moderna: "Rauschenberg", 1964 (Box PM9)
        - Galerie Ileana Sonnabend: "Untitled 1953–1954" and "Thirty-Four Dante Drawings", 1964 (Box PM9)
        - Dwan Gallery: "Rauschenberg at Dwan", 1965 (Box PM9)
        - Leo Castelli: "Robert Rauschenberg: Revolvers", 1967 (Box PM9)
        - Galerie Ileana Sonnabend: "Rauschenberg: 25 Dessins", 1968 (Box PM9)
        - Leo Castelli: "White Paintings 1951", 1968 (Box PM9)
        - Museum of Modern Art: "Rauschenberg: Soundings", 1968 (Box PM9)
        - Ace Gallery, Los Angeles: "Robert Rauschenberg: Carnal Clocks", 1969 (Box PM9)
        - Leo Castelli: "Carnal Clocks", 1969 (Box PM9)
        - Douglas Gallery: "Carnal Clocks", 1969 (Box PM9)
        - Castelli Graphics: "Stoned Moon Series", 1969 (Box PM9)
        - Newport Harbor Art Museum: "Robert Rauschenberg in Black and White: Paintings 1962–63", 1969 (Box PM9)